<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Expandable View</string>
    <string name="title">More Detail</string>
    <string name="long_content">Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here. Details is shown here.</string>
</resources>
